Guide to the New York University Archives Photograph Collection PHOTO.00001
New York University Archives
- Washington Square Campus Buildings, 189268
  - One Fifth Avenue - Exteriors, 221188
    - One Fifth Ave., Exterior, East Side of Fifth Ave. Looking North from Washington Square North, 1948; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6519; 221193; Black and White print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 189, Folder 4, Item 4)
    - One Fifth Ave., East Side of Fifth Ave., Looking South Toward Washington Sq. Park From West Eighth St., 1948; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6521; 221194; Black and White Print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 189, Folder 4, Item 5)
    - One Fifth Ave., Looking Southeast From w. 8th St., 1948; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6523; 221195; Black and White Print (Photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 189, Folder 4, Item 6)
    - One Fifth Avenue Hotel, East Side of Fifth Avenue, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6525; 221196; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 189, Folder 4, Item 7)
    - One Fifth Ave., Exterior, Looking North at Empire State Building, May 10, 1963; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6527; 221197; Simmons, William R.; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 189, Folder 4, Item 8)
    - One Fifth Ave., Building Facade, Looking East, May 5, 1966; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6529; 221198; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 14 x 11 inches (Box 189, Folder 4, Item 9)
    - One Fifth Ave., Exterior, Bike Lanes, October 1980; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6531; 221199; Chin, Danny; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 5x8 inches (Box 189, Folder 4, Item 10)
    - One Fifth. Ave., Block University Place, Looking Northeast from Beneach Arch at Washington Square North, circa 1948; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6533; 221200; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 189, Folder 4, Item 11)
  - Two Fifth Avenue, 221201
    - Two Fifth Ave., Chancellor Chase's Residence until January 1940, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6536; 221202; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 189, Folder 5, Item 1)
    - Two Fifth Ave., Dr. Chase's Residence until January 1940, Courtyard with Fountain, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6538; 221203; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 189, Folder 5, Item 2)
    - Two Fifth Ave., South Side of West 8th Street looking West from Fifth Avenue, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6540; 221204; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 189, Folder 5, Item 3)
    - Two Fifth Ave., Chancellor Chase's Residence Until January 1940, Courtyard in the Snow, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6542; 221205; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 189, Folder 5, Item 4)
    - Two Fifth Ave., Dr. Chase's Residence up to January 1940, View of Backyard, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6544; 221206; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 189, Folder 5, Item 5)
    - Block Fifth Avenue, West Side of Fifth Ave. Looking North From Washington Square North, 1947; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6546; 221207; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 189, Folder 5, Item 6)
  - Fifth Ave. #24, 221208
    - Fifth Ave. # 24, Entrance Doorway, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6549; 221209; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 5x7 inches (Box 189, Folder 6, Item 1)
  - Courant Institute, 221210
    - Courant Building, Looking Northwest, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6522; 221211; Color Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 189, Folder 7, Item 1)
    - Warren Weaver Hall Under Construction, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6554; 221212; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 5x7 inches (Box 189, Folder 7, Item 2)
    - Courant, Gould Plaza, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6556; 221213; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 189, Folder 7, Item 3)
    - Courant, Looking Northwest, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6558; 221214; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 189, Folder 7, Item 4)
    - Courant Institute of Mathematical Sciences, Building Sign, November 1972; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6560; 221215; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 189, Folder 7, Item 5)
    - Courant Institute of Mathematical Sciences, Aerial, Looking East, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6562; 221216 (Box 189, Folder 7, Item 6)
    - Courant Institute of Mathematical Sciences, Looking Southeast, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6568; 221220; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 5x7 inches (Box 189, Folder 7, Item 7)
    - Courant Institute of Mathematical Sciences, Looking Southwest, 1973; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6570; 221221; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 189, Folder 7, Item 8)
  - D'Agostino Hall Artist's Rendering/Plans, 221217
    - Filomen D'Agostino Hall, Artist's Rendering, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6564; 221218; Pagnano, Patrick D.; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 189, Folder 8, Item 1)
    - Filomen D'Agostino Hall, Artist's Rendering Closeup, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6566; 221219; Pagnano, Patrick D.; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 189, Folder 8, Item 2)
  - D'Agostino Hall Construction, 221222
    - D'Agostino Hall, Corner of West Third and MacDougal, Aearial, Looking Southeast, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6573; 221223; Luigi Pellettieri; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 189, Folder 9, Item 1)
    - D'Agostino Law Dorm, Corner of West Third and MacDougal, Street View, Looking Southeast, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6575; 221224; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 189, Folder 9, Item 2)
    - Filomen D'Agostino Hall, Looking Southeast, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6577; 221225; Luigi Pellettieri; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 189, Folder 9, Item 3)
    - D'Agostino Hall, Interior Construction, October 1985; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6579; 221226; Pagnano, Patrick D.; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 189, Folder 9, Item 4)
    - D'Agostino Hall, Street View, Looking East, July 1986; Ua_PHOTO_001_ref6581; 221227; Pagnano, Patrick D.; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 189, Folder 9, Item 5)
    - D'Agostino Hall, Corner of West Third and MacDougal, Looking East6583, July 1986; UA_PHOTO_001_ref; 221228; Pagnano, Patrick D.; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 189, Folder 9, Item 6)
    - D'Agostino Hall, West Third Street Building Facade, Looking South, July 1986; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6585; 221229; Pagnano, Patrick D.; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 189, Folder 9, Item 7)
    - D'Agostino Hall, West Third Street Facade, Street View, Looking South, July 1986; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6587; 221230; Pagnano, Patrick D.; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 189, Folder 9, Item 8)
    - D'Agostino Hall, Aerial, Looking West, circa 1985; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6589; 221231; Pagnano, Patrick D.; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 189, Folder 9, Item 9)
    - D'Agostino Hall, New York University Law School Dormintory Construction Project Sign, July 1986; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6591; 221232; Pagnano, Patrick D.; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 189, Folder 9, Item 10)
    - D'Agostino Hall Law Dorm Under Construction, West Third Building Facade, Aerial, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6593; 221233; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 189, Folder 9, Item 11)
    - D'Agostino Hall, Corner of West Third and MacDougal, Looking Southeast, Aerial, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6595; 221234; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 189, Folder 9, Item 12)
    - D'Agostino Hall, New Law Dorm Construction Site, Aerial, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6597; 221235; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 189, Folder 9, Item 13)
  - D'Agostino Hall Interiors, 221311
    - D'Agostino Hall, Student Housing, Studio, Desk and Bed with Door, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6600; 221312; Color Print, (Photograph), 4x6 inches (Box 189, Folder 11, Item 1)
    - D'Agostino Hall, Student Housing, Studio, Desk and Bed, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6602; 221313; Color Print, (Photograph), 4x6 inches (Box 189, Folder 11, Item 2)
    - Lipton Hall Auditorium, Chairs and Podium, Undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6604; 221314; Color Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 189, Folder 11, Item 3)
    - Conference Facility, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6606; 221315; Color Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 189, Folder 11, Item 4)
    - Lipton Hall viewed from the Foyer, undated; UA_PHOTO_001)ref6608; 221316; Color Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 189, Folder 11, Item 5)
    - Faculty Club viewed from the Foyer, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref; 221317; Color Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 189, Folder 11, Item 6)
    - Reception Room, D'Agostino Hall, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6612; 221318; Color Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 189, Folder 11, Item 7)
    - The Foyer, D'Agostino Hall, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6614; 221319; Color Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 189, Folder 11, Item 8)
    - The Faculty Club, D'Agostino Hall, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6616; 221320; Color Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 189, Folder 11, Item 9)
    - The Foyer viewed from the Faculty Club, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6618; 221321; Color Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 189, Folder 11, Item 10)
    - D'Agostino Law Dorm, The Commons, Reception Room and Staircase, circa 1990; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6620; 221322; Luigi Pellettieri; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 189, Folder 11, Item 11)
    - New Library Media Center, 1987; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6622; 221323; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 189, Folder 11, Item 12)
    - Law Library Extension, Stacks and Study Table, November 1987; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6624; 221324; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 189, Folder 11, Item 13)
    - Law Library Extension, New Media Center Cubicles, November 1987; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6626; 221325; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 189, Folder 11, Item 14)
    - Faculty Dining Room, D'Agostino Hall, Looking North, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6628; 221326; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 189, Folder 11, Item 15)
    - Faculty Dining Room, D'Agostino Hall, Looking Northeast, November 1987; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6630; 221327; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 189, Folder 11, Item 16)
    - The Foyer Fireplace, D'Agostino Hall, November 1987; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6632; 221328; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 189, Folder 11, Item 17)
    - Student Dining Hall, D'Agostino Hall, Aerial View, November 1987; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6633; 221329; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 189, Folder 11, Item 18)
    - D'Agostino Hall, Law Commons, Cafeteria, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6636; 221330; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 189, Folder 11, Item 19)
    - D'Agostino Hall, Law Commons, Cafeteria, Looking North, November 1987; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6638; 221331; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 189, Folder 11, Item 20)
    - D'Agostino Hall, Student Commons, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6640; 221332; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches
  - Founders Monument - Gould Plaza, 221451
    - Grace Church, Spire Close-up, 17 January 1978; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6643; 221452; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 5x7 inches (Box 190, Folder 1, Item 1)
    - Founders Monument at the University Heights Campus, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6645; 221453; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 190, Folder 1, Item 2)
    - Founders Monument at the University Heights Campus, Trees and Buildings in Background, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6647; 221454; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 190, Folder 1, Item 3)
    - Founders Monument at the University Heights Campus, Trees and Bright Sky in Background, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6649; 221455; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 190, Folder 1, Item 4)
    - Founders Monument at the University Heights Campus, Base with Inscription, 1 November 1972; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6651; 221456; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 190, Folder 1, Item 5)
    - Founders Monument at the University Heights Campus, Spire Close-up, 1 November 1972; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6653; 221457; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 190, Folder 1, Item 6)
    - Founders Monument at the University Heights Campus, Inscription Close-up, 30 November 1972; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6655; 221458; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 190, Folder 1, Item 7)
    - Founders Monument at the University Heights Campus, Base with Inscription Close-up, November 1, 1972; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6657; 221535; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 190, Folder 1, Item 8)
    - Founders Monument at the University Heights Campus, Lower Half with Buildings and Cars in Background, November 1, 1972; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6659; 221536; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 190, Folder 1, Item 9)
    - Founders Monument at the University Heights Campus, Buildings and Cars in Background, November 1, 1972; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6661; 221537; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 190, Folder 1, Item 10)
    - Founders Monument at the University Heights Campus, Buildings, Flagpole and Buildings, November 1, 1972; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6663; 221538; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 190, Folder 1, Item 11)
    - Construction of Founders Monument in Gould Plaza at Tisch Hall, May 5, 1973; UA_PHOTO_ref6665; 221539; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 190, Folder 1, Item 12)
    - Founders Monument, Relocation to Gould Plaza on Washington Square Park, May 5, 1973; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6667; 221540; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 190, Folder 1, Item 13)
    - Founders Monument Base, Relocation to Gould Plaza on Washington Square Park, May 5, 1973; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6669; 221541; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 190, Folder 1, Item 14)
    - Founders Monument at Gould Plaza, Looking Northwest, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6671; 221542; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 190, Folder 1, Item 15)
    - Founders Monument at Gould PLaza, Looking West, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6672; 221543; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 5x8 inches (Box 190, Folder 1, Item 16)
    - Founders Monument at Gould Plaza, Looking Up with Trees in Plaza, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6674; 221544; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 190, Folder 1, Item 17)
    - Founders Monument at Gould Plaza, Looking West with Trees, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6676; 221545; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 190, Folder 1, Item 18)
    - Founders Monument at Gould Plaza, Close-up Gargoyle Detail, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6678; 221546; Heighton, Tom; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 190, Folder 1, Item 19)
    - Founders Monument at Gould Plaza, Close-up Detail of Gargoyles, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6680; 221547; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 190, Folder 1, Item 20)
    - Gould Plaza, Looking South, April 13, 1982; UA_PHOTO_001_re6682; 221564; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 5x8 inches (Box 190, Folder 1, Item 21)
    - Student Sitting at Gould Plaza with Founders Monument in Background, Looking West, April 1982; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6684; 221565; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 190, Folder 1, Item 22)
    - Gould Plaza, Aerial View, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6686; 221566; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 190, Folder 1, Item 23)
    - Gould Memorial Plaza, Tisch Hall, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6688; 221567; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 5x8 inches (Box 190, Folder 1, Item 24)
    - Gould Plaza Dedication Plaque, Looking West, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref692; 221569; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 5x5 inches (Box 190, Folder 1, Item 26)
    - Gould Plaza, Students Reading and Chatting, April 1982; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6694; 221570; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 5x8 inches (Box 190, Folder 1, Item 27)
    - Gould Memorial Plaza and Tisch Hall, Looking South, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6690; 221568; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 5x8 inches (Box 190, Folder 1, Item 25)
    - President John M. Hester and Jerry Goldman Chairman of the Students Senators Council of the University Senate, Aerial View of Founders Monument, May 21, 1973; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6697; 221571; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 190, Folder 1, Item 26)
    - President John M. Hester and Jerry Goldman, Chairman of the Student Senators Council of the University Senate with Founders Memorial Rededication Plaque, May 21, 1973; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6699; 221572 (Box 190, Folder 1, Item 27)
    - Construction of the Founders Monument in front of Tisch Building, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6850; 222316; Rodriguez, Robert F.; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 190, Folder 1, Item 28)
  - La Maison Francaise - Exterior, 221648
    - La Maison Francaise, Students Walking in Front of Building, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6701; 221649; Color Print, (Photograph), 5x7 inches (Box 190, Folder 2, Item 1)
    - La Maison Francaise Sign, Student Standing in Front of Building, Summer Bulletin Picture, 1991; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6703; 221650; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 5x7 inches (Box 190, Folder 2, Item 2)
    - La Maison Francaise, 16 Washington Mews, New Sailors' Snug Harbor Property at Time of Photo, Looking South, circa 1946; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6705; 221652; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 190, Folder 2, Item 3)
    - La Maison Francaise, Looking West, April 26, 1957; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6707; 221653; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 190, Folder 2, Item 4)
    - La Maison Francaise, 16 Washington Mews, New Sailors' Snug Harbor Property at Time of Photo, Looking West, circa 1946; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6709; 221654; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 190, Folder 2, Item 5)
    - La Maison Francaise, Looking Southwest at East Side of University Place from Washington Mews, April 1955; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6711; 221655; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 190, Folder 2, Item 6)
    - La Maison Francaise, Front Facade and Mews Entrance, January 16, 1969; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6713; 221656; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 190, Folder 2, Item 7)
    - La Maison Francase, Artists Rendering, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6715; 221657; Color Print, (Photograph), 4x5 inches (Box 190, Folder 2, Item 8)
    - Hostess, La Maison Francaise, Mrs. Ada Mordacques Squiers, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6717; 221658; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 5x7 inches (Box 190, Folder 2, Item 9)
    - La Maison Francaise, Arthur Shatz, undated; Ua_PHOTO_001_ref6719; 221659; Shatz, Arthur; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 4x6 inches (Box 190, Folder 2, Item 10)
    - La Maison Francaise, Doorway Entrance Close-up, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6721; 221660; Shatz, Arthur; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 5x7 inches (Box 190, Folder 2, Item 11)
    - La Maison Francaise, Building Facade with Student Walking in Front, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6723; 221661; Shatz, Arthur; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 5x8 inches (Box 190, Folder 2, Item 12)
    - La Maison Francaise, Washington Mews Arch and Front Facade, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6725; 221662; Forster, R; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 190, Folder 2, Item 13)
    - La Maison Francaise, 2-4 1/2 University Place and 16 Washington Mews, West Side of University Place, circa 1946; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6727; 221663; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 190, Folder 2, Item 14)
    - La Maison Francaise, Looking West with Buildings in Background, April 1955; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6729; 221664; Simmons, William R.; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 190, Folder 2, Item 15)
    - La Maison Francaise Proposed Facade, Artists Rendering, circa 1955; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6731; 221665; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 190, Folder 2, Item 16)
    - La Maison Francaise, Old Front Door Close-up, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6733; 221666; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 190, Folder 2, Item 17)
    - La Maison Francaise, Old Front Door and Facade, 1965; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6735; 221667; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 3 1/2x4 1/2 inches (Box 190, Folder 2, Item 18)
    - La Maison Francaise, Old Front Door and Facade Illuminated, 1965; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6737; 221668; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 4 1/2x 3 1/2 inches (Box 190, Folder 2, Item 19)
    - La Maison Francaise, Old Facade, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6739; 221669; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 190, Folder 2, Item 20)
    - La Maison Francaise, Facade and Mews Archway, Looking Southwest, April 26, 1957; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6741; 221670; Gooen, Irwin; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 190, Folder 2, Item 21)
    - La Maison Francaise, View From Building Across the Street, May 12, 1965; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6743; 221671; Seligson, Stanley; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 190, Folder 2, Item 22)
    - La Maison Francaise, Reading Room with French Map, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6745; 221672; Shatz, Arthur; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 5x7 inches (Box 190, Folder 2, Item 23)
  - La Maison Francaise - Events, 221673
    - Book Signing with Tom Bishop at La Maison Francaise, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6748; 221674; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 5x7 inches (Box 190, Folder 2, Item 1)
    - Reading of Beckett's Poetry and Prose at La Maison Francaise, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6750; 221675; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 190, Folder 3, Item 4)
      New York University -- Washington Square Campus.; New York University -- Buildings.; Oliva, L. Jay (Lawrence Jay), 1933-2014
    - Colloquium on Rural Life in Urban Society Today, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6752; 221769; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 190, Folder 3, Item 3)
    - Mayor of Barcelona Speaking at La Maison Francaise, March 24, 1983; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6754; 221770; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 190, Folder 3, Item 4)
    - Recital by Hugues Cuenod at La Maison Francaise Accompanied By David Noakes, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6756; 221772; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 190, Folder 3, Item 5)
    - Lecture by Poet Francois Ponge at La maison Francaise, December 16, 1965; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6758; 221773; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 190, Folder 3, Item 6)
    - Fashion Show, La Maison Francaise, October 15, 1974; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6760; 221774; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 190, Folder 3, Item 7)
    - Lecture by Composer and Conductor Pierre Boulez, February 23, 1972; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6762; 221789; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 190, Folder 3, Item 8)
  - La Maison Francaise - Interiors, 221790
    - La Maison Francaise Sitting Room with Stage, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6765; 221791; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 5x8 inches (Box 190, Folder 4, Item 1)
    - La Maison Francaise, Staircase Close-up, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6767; 221792; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 190, Folder 4, Item 2)
    - La Maison Francaise, Chandelier, 1986; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6769; 221809; Black and White print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 190, Folder 4, Item 3)
    - La Maison, Francaise, Fireplace and Mirror, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6771; 221810; Black and White print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 190, Folder 4, Item 4)
    - La Maison, Francaise, Tapestry, 1960; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6773; 221812; Black and White Print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 190, Folder 4, Item 5)
  - Fraternity Houses, 3-5 Washington Place, 221811